Why when kiva moved from Ukraine to
Почему когда кива Переехал из Украины в
Russia about the average level of intelligence
Россию о средний уровень интеллекта
increased in both
возрос в обоих
countries Where are you from I am from
странах Вы откуда Я из
Bryansk And you from
Брянска А вы из
Kursk
Курска
wonderful can you name the capital of
замечательно можете назвать столицу
Iceland Andrey Rick
Исландии Андрей Рик
yavik wonderful so good I accept
явик замечательно так хорошо Я принимаю
this fight let's do it this way and the capital of Norway
этот бой давайте так а столица Норвегии
No idea Oslo donkey not  spy
Без понятия Осло осла не подсматривать
Let's go I'm not spying Let's go
Давай би я Я не подсматриваю Давай давай
battle battle Let's go capital of
битва битва Давай Давайте столица
Burkina Faso Burkina Faso I don't know Well the
Буркина Фасо Буркина Фасо не знаю А ну
first two letters ua
первые две буквы
ua Yes I don't know Well that's how it happens Andrey You
уа Да не знаю Ну так вот Андрей бывает
see when you just
Понимаете вот когда вы вот просто
lose
проигрываете
the name how it happens uagadougou
назви как она так бывает уагадугу
uagadougou Holy [ __ ]  In short, so good
уагадугу [__] Короче так хорошо
capital of New Zealand No idea
столица Новой Зеландии Без понятия
Wellington
велингтон
Sorry, I just didn't get into it, never
Извините просто не вникал ни разу не
got into it, Africa, specialist, I understood No,
вникал Африке специалист я понял Нет
you know, why, specialist Why I'm
знаете почему специалист Почему Мне вот
interested, you know, it's always
интересно вот знаете вот всегда
been interesting to talk to you
интересно было с вами С вами поговорить
I always tell you honestly, honestly Everything Not
всегда я вам честно говорю чест Всё Не
if you want  not a quiz Let's talk
если хочешь не викторину Давай поговорим
about another topic No not a quiz not a
на другую тему Нет не викторину не
quiz Let's just skip
викторину Давайте вот пропустим просто
all these moments  yes I was from the state Here is
эти все моменты всё да я из гос было Вот
your opinion regarding everything that is
ваше мнение отношении вот всего что
happening Here is really I
происходит Вот вот реально я вам на
fully fully understood everything is super we
полном на полном понял всё супер мы
caught those with whom you can
поймали тем с кем можно нормально
talk normally Let's I am from the city of
поговорить Давайте я из города
Khmelnitsky and Ukraine How do I know
Хмельницке и Украина Вы откуда я знаю
where you are from I am getting to know you  where from I'm
откуда вы я ж знакомлюсь Вы откуда Я же
telling you I'm from Bre again I'm from Bre then
вам говорю я из бре ещё раз я из бре то
we first we started from scratch
мы сначала мы же с чистого листа начали
Bryansk Bryansk Let's start from scratch again
Брянск Брянск Давай ещё раз начинаем с
I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
чистого листа Я из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine Where are you from Bryansk wonderfully
Украина Вы откуда замечательно Брянск
understood what you're talking about an hour of roulette
понял о чём общаетесь час рулетки
Lord
Господи
Andrey I have  such a Prelude I have such a
Андрей у меня такая Прелюдия Уменя такая
pre s e I heard you again your
пре е раз я вас услышал ещё раз ваше
attitude to everything that is happening Okay I
отношение ко всему происходящему О'кей я
treat this as a
отношусь к этому как
global good and now how do you
глобальне хорошо а теперь как вы
feel about the fact that Russia attacked
относитесь к тому что Россия напала на
Ukraine
Украину
depending on what is
в зависимости от того что
happening how do you answer this
происходит вам как ответить на этот
question as you wish And you clearly Ask a
вопрос как хотите А вы чётко вот Задайте
question I will answer you how do you feel about the
вопрос я Вам отвечу как вы относитесь к
fact that Russia is on the shelves Ask
тому что Россия по полочкам Задайте
a question I asked the question as I asked You
вопрос Я задал вопрос так как я задал Вы
answer I answer as  here you asked
отвечаете отвечаю так как вот ты задал
a question a clear question what is the
вопрос чёткий вопрос кий
answer So as I think it is necessary you
ответ Во так как я считаю нужным ты
answer As you think it is necessary I
отвечаешь Так как ты считаешь нужным Я
ask How do you feel about
задаю Как ты относишься к тому что
Russia attacking Ukraine great
Россия напала на Украину великолепно
super your question my
супер твой вопрос мой
question How do you feel about
вопрос Как вы относитесь к тому что
Russia attacking
Россия на полную
Ukraine negatively  negative Okay my
Украину негативно негативно Хорошо мой
question do you support the fact that Russia
вопрос ты поддерживаешь то что Россия
attacked Ukraine in no
напала на Украину ни в коем
way answered yes your in my question
случае ответил да тво во мой вопрос
is great Here is what is happening to me
замечательно Вот то что происходит мне
you know once again once again yes I will explain
вот знаете ещё раз ещё раз да я объясню
Simply I am interested In general and on the whole
Просто Вот мне интересно В общем и целом
can you reasonably express your
можете аргументированно выразить ваше
opinion  in relation to everything without any
мнение в отношении всего без каких-то
bias of any moments I
предвзятое каких-то моментов мне я не
will not even interrupt please Yes here is
буду даже перебивать пожалуйста Да вот
my Here is my question from beginning to end
мой Вот мой вопрос от начала и до конца
I understood the attitude to the processes that
понял отношение к процессам которые
occur from beginning to end in
происходят от начала и до конца в
relation to everything quite clearly so
отношении всего довольно однозначно так
I do not support  everything bad and
я не поддерживаю всё плохое и
I support everything good yes from the very
поддерживаю всё хорошее да с самого
beginning negative tendencies began
начала начались негативные тенденции
that continue until the very end in all
которые идут до самого конца во всех
these aspects I think that it is necessary to
этих аспектах Я считаю что нужно сделать
consolidate and make
консолидированном и сделать хорошего
more good and less bad
больше плохого меньше
no questions no questions in fact
нет вопросов нет вопросов на самом деле
very competently and very clearly answered
очень грамотно и очень чётко ответили
good
хорошо
good good  Now now my question
хорошо хорошо Теперь теперь мой вопрос
let's give any
давайте давайте любой
So how much do you estimate the number of people killed
Так сколько вы оцениваете погибших людей
from Russia in the war in
из России на войне в
Ukraine well I can't estimate the number of
Украине ну я не могу оценивать на самом
people killed in Ukraine on Russia
деле погибших людей в Украине ны России
from Ukraine's side from everything I
со стороны Украины со стороны всего я не
can't estimate them For the simple reason
могу их оценивать По той простой причине
that  I don't know this Elementary
то что я не знаю это Элементарно
you understand each each side in any
понимаете каждая каждая сторона в любом
case will downplay its losses in
случае будет принижать свои потери в
any case your country will downplay
любом случае ваша страна будет принижать
the losses My country will downplay the losses
потери Моя страна будет принижать потери
and so on I can't say I don't know
и так далее я не могу сказать я не знаю
this Emen just a question about
это Эмен просто вопро пом
approximate they
приблизительным ония
don't know andre po  oh everything is fine your
не знаю анре по ой всё хорошо ваш
question is wonderful you are
вопрос замечательно вы сегодня
very-very some kind of peculiar simple today do
очень-очень какой-то своеобразно простой
n't you
вам не
think if this is a question answer it doesn't seem it
кажется если это вопрос ответ не кажется
doesn't seem it's just usually you are
не кажется просто обычно вы вы более
more such a peculiar relaxed you
более такой своеобразно раскрепощённый
understand you talk more And
понимаете Вы больше разговариваете А
today you are less times for some reason I don't know
сегодня вы меньше раз почему-то не знаю
why ok let's take your question so my
почему хорошо давайте ваш вопрос так мой
question
вопрос
Where do you think Russia could
Как вы считаете куда Россия могла бы
put all these resources money that
деть все эти ресурсы денежные которые
it spent on the
она потратила на
war in various aspects in various
войну в различные аспекты в различные
aspects to give to the people and so on and so
аспекты дать народу и так далее и тому
forth absolutely various aspects
подобное абсолютно различные аспекты
Russia could spend its resources
Россия могла бы потратить свои ресурсы
that it  spent on war example
которые она потратила на войну примеру
give me why not yes Why  whether or
дать мне почему бы нет да Почему бы и
not I
нет я
would understand I'm not a dummy either
бы понимаете Я тоже ну не пальцем
Give me
деланный Дайте мне
money Elementary Yes
денег Элементарно Да
elementary Good good What do you
элементарно Хорошо хорошо Как вы
think let's say What do you think
считаете допустим Как вы считаете
Donald Trump will become
Дональд Трамп придёт
president What will happen after he comes
президентом Что будет после прихода его
[music]
[музыка]
what will happen after Trump becomes
что после того как Трамп станет
president after he comes
президентом после прихода его будет
Donald Trump's five-year presidential term is
пятилетний срок президентства дональда
wonderful as with as opp Stop
трампа замечательно как с как опп Стоп
This is a question question Let's Question who do
Это вопрос вопрос жа Давайте Вопрос кого
you see as the ruler of Russia after
вы видите правителем России после смерти
Putin's death This is a difficult question Andrey
Путина Это сложный вопрос Андрей
question So far no
вопрос Пока
one At the moment
никого Вот в данный момент
no one this is a clear answer okay yes clear
никого это чёткий ответ окей да чёткий
this is your answer Yes
это ж ваш ответ Да
wonderful wonderful  Okay then
замечательно прекрасно Хорошо тогда
let's talk about Donald Trump Let's
давайте мы про дональда трампа
continue what Donald Trump will do
Продолжим что сделает Дональд трам вот
in your
по вашему
opinion after he comes to power I don't know
мнению после прихода своего не знаю к
I think that after he comes to
власти Я думаю что после прихода к
power after the inauguration Trump will go into the
власти после инаугурации Трамп зайдёт в
Oval Office of the White House sit on a
овальный кабинет Белого дома сядет на
chair put his feet up on the table and
стульчик закинет ноги на стол и
say life
скажет жизнь
a  great I would do the same in his place I would
а замечательно Я б так на его месте я б
do the same in his place the first
на его месте реально так сделал первый
day that I would do the same the question is uh don't
день шо так бы сделал вопрос такой ээ не
you think that in Russia the Chechens  And
кажется ли вам что в России чеченцам И в
especially Kadyrovets are allowed what is
особенности кадыровца позволено то что
not allowed to
не позволено
Russians
русским
of course in different cities many things are allowed
безусловно в различных городах позволено
of course But again it
многое безусловно Но это опять же
depends on where someone is
зависит от того где кто Находится
Let's So where someone is in
Давайте Так где кто Находится в
different cities many things are allowed in
различных городах позволено многое в
different cities nothing is allowed everything is
различных не позволено ничего всё
elementary normal answer Yes yes that's
элементарное нормальный ответ Да да это
it  your answer yes Sorry I just
же ваш ответ да Извините я просто может
maybe yes we will not evaluate each other's answers
быть да мы не оценим ответы друг друга
Yes what question What kind of answers Yes
Да какой вопрос Какой такие ответы Да
everything Yes sorry Let's do it this way
всё Да извините Вот давайте так
oppositionist what is his name
хорошо оппозиционер как как зовут
Sorry maybe you can tell me
Извините може может быть подскажете
Muravlevsky Muravlev What is his name
муравлёв ский муравлёв Как как зовут его
your
ваш
oppositionist What is your attitude  to his
оппозиционер Как вы относитесь к его
activities to
деятельности к
whom to your Ozi what oppositionist
кому к вашему Ози какому оппозиционер
What is his name Sorry please I don't
Как зовут его Простите пожалуйста я не
know what kind exactly how mu don't know
знаю какого именно как му не знаете
yes let's
да давайте
google
загугли
Poroshenko No not with us Poroshenko
Порошенко Нет не у нас Порошенко
opposition not Tymoshenko Well no well what Well
оппозиции не Тимошенко Ну нет ну какой
what Poroshenko Andrey well you have a
Ну какой Порошенко Андрей ну вы такое
feeling that you  you don't understand at all
ощущение что вы вообще не понимаете о
what I'm talking about I don't understand rabbi if I'm not
чём я говорю не понимаю равв если я не
mistaken I know
ошибаюсь зна
I hear really really
слышу реально реально
Andrey  really I'm hearing for the first time murav not
Андрей реально я Впервые слышу мурав не
okay find find on Google What kind of
порядок найди найди на Гугли Что за
Muravlev Muravlevskiy is this
муравлёв муравлёв
really Yeah
ский прям ну реально Да
really Let's
реально Давайте
find
найдём
Muravyed No not an ant unfortunately
Муравьед Нет не муравья к сожалению
Let's find some kind of Mura gon maybe
Давайте найдём мура гон какой-то может
Muraev Forgive me please but why Oh
мураев Простите пожалуйста а почему О
oppositionist Muraev Lord excuse me yes
оппозиционер мураев Господи извините да
And what  he is an oppositionist he is neither a
А что он оппозиционер он не это ни
deputy nor a politician And who is he Who is he
депутат ни политик А кто он Кто он
anyway Muraev This is some dude
вообще такой мураев Это какой-то чувак
he does not even live in Ukraine
он даже не в Украине
Excuse me please a
Извините пожалуйста кандидат в
presidential candidate if there is an election a
президенты если будет избрание кандидат
presidential candidate I mean he is a candidate for
в президент В смысле он кандидат в
president Who does he live at all And you
президент Кто он вообще не живёт А вы
think he is not a presidential candidate and
считаете он не кандидат в президенты а
he cannot be a presidential candidate
он не может быть кандидатом в президенты
by law Why Because a
по закону Почему Потому что кандидат в
presidential candidate must
президенты должен
live in Ukraine for the last 5 or 10 years
проживать последние там 5 или 10 лет в
Yeah and he lives he does not live in
Украине Угу а он проживает о живёт не в
Ukraine  in Ukraine not in Ukraine yes that
Украине не в Украине не в Украине да то
is he understands correctly he gives
есть он правильно понимаю он даёт
interviews all other moments in your
интервью все остальные моменты вашей
country you have  in his homeland but he does not
стране у вас на родине но он не
live he is not in Ukraine he
проживает он не в Украине он не
is not in Ukraine He left Ukraine
находится в Украине Он выехал из Украины
great Let's understand your question this way
замечательно Давайте ваш вопрос так
The question is which of the
понял Вопрос кого вы вообще из
Ukrainian politicians
украинских политиков
do you know
знаете
I know it's
я это
difficult no one really No really I
сложно никого на самом Нет на самом деле
know really I know your only one
знаю на самом деле знаю единственный ваш
political scientist what's his name I
политек которого как его зовут я прошу
apologize not prepared Andrey you know not prepared
прощение не подготовлен Андрей знаете не
but
но
But your ex You probably can tell
Но ваш бывший Вы наверное подскажете
Andrey You probably can tell your
Андрей Вы наверное подскажете ваш
former deputy president supreme
бывший заместитель президента верховный
there Who is he Who is he Who Who Who Who
там Кто он Кто он Кто Кто Кто Кто Кто
Tell me what is his name
Скажите как его
My God
зовут Боже мой
there are no anteaters there
муравьедов нет
was Muraev  was
был мураев был
Muraev that at the moment I ask a question
мураев что данный момент задаю вопрос
about
про
the arrestovic How do you feel about all
арестовича Как вы относитесь ко всем
the presentations of
изложения
it I don't even look for And he
его даже не смотрю за А он
still Yes he is where he lives he is Yes
ещё Да он есть где он живёт он есть Есть
Yes
Есть
of course Where does he live don't look at all I don't
конечно Где он жит не смотрите вообще не
know he lives at all you don't know who this is I know
зна он жит вобще не знаете кто это знаю
In short, he was once an actor Yes, I
Короче он когда-то он актёр Да я его я
remember him from a feature film, he
его помню по фильму художественному он
played a girl named Lucy there, Aristovich, yes,
играл девушку Люсю там аристович да
Aristovich Well,
аристович Ну про одного и того же
we are talking about the same person or maybe about
человека говорит ми или может быть про
different people Are you on the computer now  I'll
разных Ты сейчас за компьютером я да
type in Google aristovich Lyusenka type in
вбей в Гугле арестович Люсенька вбей
Yeah So let's go I'll also type in
Ага Так давай я Я сейчас тоже вбей
aristovich Lyusenka Come on, come on, type in
арестович Люсенька Давай давай ж вбивай
both aristo I'm sorry, please, that I
обю аресто я Извини пожалуйста что на
have to type in aristovich Lyusenka
ещё раз надо в бить арестович Люсенька
Aristovich Lyusenka again yeah, that's
аристович Люсенька
great, there is such a thing, but it's not
замечательно есть такое но это не
a work of art, what kind of work is it
художественное произведение это
- I don't know what a scene is. This is a scene.
какая-то сценка не знаю это сценка это
This is a clipping from a
вырезка из фильма А это это вырезка из
film. Yes, great. That is, you ca
фильма Да замечательно То есть вы
n't rate Alexey Ristovich at all. I
Алексея ристо вича не расценить вообще Я
don't know. I know him as an actor. I just
не знаю я его знаю как актёра Я просто
remember watching Russian TV series. Yes, he
помню сериалы смотрел российский Да он
starred in Lyusenka. What kind of  -
там снимался в Люсенька Ну каких-то
characters like that, well, what else is he
персонажей таких типа ну а что он ещё он
still filming with you there in
ещё до сих пор снимается у вас там в
Russia with us in Russia, yes, Alexey
России у нас в России да Алексей
Aristovich Probably I dont know Hes filming with you
аристович Наверное я не знаю Он же у вас
Yes, I dont know, he was your
снима Да не знаю он у вас был там
deputy president there, my question is not
заместителем президента мой вопрос не
was he a deputy president Nida
был он заместителем президента Нида не
was not And who was he find find Look you
был А кем он был найди найди Смотри ты
already the second time no need  who he was I don't
уже второй раз не надо кем он был я не
know who he was he wasn't for no need who
знаю кем он был он не был за не надо кем
he was because I know the
он был потому что я знаю заместителей
president's deputies among the president's deputies
президента среди заместителей президента
there was no surname Arrestovich there was no okay
не было фамилии арестович не было хорошо
let's continue It was you who
давайте продолжаем Это вы что-то
came up with something in short it was you who came up with We
придумали короче это вы придумали У нас
don't even have  positions of deputy
нету Даже должности заместитель
president of
президента
Ukraine you come on come on your question
Украине вы давайте давайте вопрос ваш
I want at least one deputy president in
мне хоть одного заместителя президента в
Ukraine
Украине
Let's have the position of deputy
Давайте чтоб было должность заместитель
president a great
президента прекрасный
question Yeah
вопрос Угу
great deputy of the office of the president
прекрасно заместитель офиса президента
Let's express ourselves incorrectly Sorry
Давайте неправильно выразился Простите
please deputy of the office of the president
пожалуйста заместитель офиса президента
this is normal deputy is the office of the
это нормально заместитель есть офис
president this is not a president at all he is to the
президента это вообще не президент он к
president  office of the president Andrey
президенту итель офиса президента Андрей
Who who deputy office of the president
Кто кто заместитель офиса президента
Aristovich was never
аристович был не было никогда
deputy office of the president google
заместителем офиса президента загуглите
please did not have the internet at hand did not have the
пожалуйста у интернет под рукой не был у
internet at hand maybe yes let's
вас под рукой интернет может да по давай
look google Let's
смотри загуглите Давайте
no Read How it says there You have then
нету Прочитайте Как там пишет У вас
look
значит смотрите
I read freelance adviser of the office
читаю внештатный советник офиса
president owl stop advisor what
президента сове стоп советник какой
freelance advisor Sorry owl so
внешт советник Извините сове так ещё раз
look again Yes don't notice What is freelance
смотри Да не заме Что такое внештатный
What is
Что такое
freelance the one that Yes freelance
внештатный тот который Да внештатный -
is the one that is not on staff Yes he doesn't
это тот который не в штате Да он не
have a salary  he is not listed anywhere Yes,
имеет зарплаты он Не числится нигде Да
he generally has millions of freelance advisers
он вообще нештатных советников миллионы
great yes that is just I once again
замечательно да то есть просто я ещё ещё
your question my question once again I give
раз ваш вопрос мой вопрос ещё раз даю
you I give you a question Okay my question eh
вам даю вам вопрос О'кей мой вопрос э
Why when kiwa Moved from Ukraine to
Почему когда кива Переехал из Украины в
Russia when what once again Why when
Россию когда что ещё раз Почему когда
kiva Moved from Ukraine to Russia the
кива Переехал из Украины в Россию
average level of intelligence has increased in
средний уровень интеллекта возрос в
both countries can you name it Who
обоих странах можешь се назвать Кто
is kiva Ilya kiva the oppositionist had
такой кива Илья кива оппозиционер был
absolutely no idea look kiva
без понятия абсолютно посмотри кива
google Ilya kiva let me google it not about
загугли Илья кива давай загуглю не про
he has a cool kiva yes yes Ilya kiva kiva kiva
прикольна у него кива да да Илья кива
Ilya kiva yes
кива кива Илья кива да
Yes Ilya  kiva now now now
Да Илья кива сейчас сечас
cool Okay cool Why
сечас прикольно Окей прикольно Почему
when Ilya kiva moved from Ukraine to
когда Илья кива Переехал из Украины в
Russia the average IQ level increased in both
Россию средний уровень IQ возрос в обоих
countries I have no idea who is who
странах Понятия не имею и кто кто это
at all This is a logical problem Why
вообще Вот это логическая задача Почему
when I moved from the
когда пере из
average IQ level increased in both
средний уровень IQ возрос в обоих
countries Well probably smart enough  the
странах Ну вероятно достаточно умный
person I don't know
человек не знаю
absolutely I don't know at all you
абсолютно вот вообще не знаю
see probably a very smart person I
понимаете вероятно очень умный человек
don't know If you fired him then
не знаю Если вы его уволили значит
[music]
[музыка]
you we not only fired him so we
вы мы его не только уволили Так мы его
def him you
дефи вы его
def him yes
дефи да
according to your understanding denazification in
по вашему пониманию денацификация в
Russia and in Russia This is denazification in
России а в России Это денацификация в
Russia and after the murder or Kiva the
России да и после убийства или кивы
average IQ level in Russia
средний уровень IQ в России
dropped And excuse me please That is
понизился А извините пожалуйста То есть
he
он правильно
understands correctly You are very I  I just don't know Andrey
понимаю Ты очень Я просто не знаю Андрей
I just don't know this is a colleague of this
Я просто не знаю это коллега этого
Muravyedov Muraev or Muravlev
муравьедова мураева или там муравлёва
I don't remember them No he is Muraev or
мне их не запоминаю Нет он мураев или
whatever his name is What is
как он зовут Как
his Anteater huh Well kiwi Yes Anteater and
его муравьедов да Ну киви Да Муравьед и
kiwi I remember them like that this kiwi he was
киви Я их так запо вот этот киви он был
this friend of Muravyedov kiwi  already
это другом муравьедова киви уже
Muravyedova soon so good
муравьедова скоро так хорошо
question Here you are purely what yes yes your
вопрос Вот вы вот чисто что да да твой
question Do you think that at the
вопрос Вы считаете то что на данный
moment
момент
what is
то что
provided to the
предоставляют
Ukrainian I don't know what to call it Okay
украинской не знаю как это назвать Окей
good Ukrainian Federation let's say
хорошо украинской Федерации допустим
yes what is
да то что
provided do you think that you
предоставляют вы считаете то что вы не
will not give
будете не отдавать
anything  I understand correctly that they
ничего правильно понимаю больше того нам
will give us even more. The fact is that
ещё больше будут давать Дело в том что
at the base it was decided
на базе было принято решение
that the
что
ladies from Ax Fi are doing that is America and
дам изн акс фи делают то есть Америка и
other countries take the confiscated
другие страны берут конфискованные
assets of the Russian Federation and supply
активы Российской Федерации поставляют
them to their factories. Yes, they pay for their
их на свои заводы Да проплачивает ихние
factories and they work at full capacity. That is,
заводы в полную катушку работают То есть
at the expense of the Russian Federation, the deficit of the
за счёт Российской Федерации дефицит
Russian Federation is
Российскую Федерацию
absolutely rare. I'm sorry, but I don't think so.
абсолютно я Извините но я так не считаю
I don't think so. I think that you are one
я так не считаю я считаю что Вы один
of Yes, you  understood one of which
из Да вы поняли один из чего у мне
by the way in my chat they write that you are rare
кстати в чате пишут что вы редкостный
in general I by the way well I think so Well
вообще я кста ну Я кстати так считаю Ну
great I'm with you once Okay let's have
замечательно Я со вас раз Хорошо давайте
your question so I asked it in my opinion
ваш вопрос так я же задал его по-моему
or not
или нет
no so good And yes you asked it now
нет так хорошо А да вы же задали теперь
my question Who heads the Government of the
мой вопрос Кто возглавляет Правительство
Russian
Российской
Federation Well,
Федерации Ну
this is well at the moment or what yes yes Well,
это ну на данный момент или что да да Ну
naturally Vladimir Vladimirovich no that
естественно владими Владимирович нет то
is
есть
look google zagu tevo zaguli
смотри загугли загу тево загули пря
right now Government of the Russian Federation
сечас Правительство Российской Федерации
e
е
va a little bit a little bit heads the
ва немножко немножко возглавляет
government Who heads the right
правительство Кто возглавляет пра
heads Who Who heads the
возглавляет Кто Кто возглавляет принятие
decision-making not  I said Who is the head of the
решений не я сказал Кто возглавляет
Government of the Russian Federation
Правительство Российской Федерации
Mishustin Well, this was already suggested to you in the chat
Мишустин Ну так это это уже тебе в чате
No, no one in Cha this is in the chat in the
подсказали Нет никто в Ча это в чате в
chat of the guy Yes, no one just  chat Okay
чате поца Да никто просто чате Хорошо
then quickly tell me who is the head of the State Duma what is
тогда быстро скажи кто глава Госдумы что
the head of the State Duma who No idea You see
глава Госдумы кто Без понятия Вот видишь
in short Volodin no no really No idea
короче Володин нене реально Без понятия
really No idea Yes because they
реально Без понятия Да потому что тебе
wrote to you in the chat mishti That is, you
написали в чате мишти То есть ты что-то
know something nobody wrote
знаешь никто писал
nobody you know about this is a common
никто ты знаешь про вот обычная
feature of everyone  Russians these
особенность всех россиян ских этих
e they know everything about Ukrainian
э они всё знают про украинских
anteaters some damn kiwi in short there is
муравьедов каких-то блин киви короче там
also Shmi Arrestovich Yes but they don't know who
ещё шми арестович Да но не знают кто у
heads their government And who
них возглавляет правительство И кто у
heads their State Duma So why so
них возглавляет Госдуму Так почему
why so
так что почему так
that's all
вот и всё
yes they know that we have  some kind of
да они знают что у нас какой-то там
Muraev they know something else In short I
мураев они знают что-то там ещё Короче я
don't know they know anything they don't know
не знаю что угодно знают они не знают
who their head of government is and
кто у них глава правительства уряду да
who their prime minister is and they don't know who
кто премьер-министр у них и не знают кто
their head of the State Duma is
у них глава государственнной Думы
subscribe to my Telegram right now  axis
подпишись на ми Telegram прямо зараз ось
vin a
вин а
popk ce duzhe and duzhe livo YouTube Zaga
попк це дуже и дуже ливо YouTube Зага
us through scarg or in ny ban and duzhe a
нас через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже
lot of videos I will not show to people  sometimes does not
багато вдео не показу людям вчасно не
show information about streams That's
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
why we Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
are written right now and while there are in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm videos there is also interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will always sing operational
информация и мы пон ва тма пой оператив
links independently in order to show you
звязок незалежно в того чи покаже вам
about this YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
про це YouTube Слава украини пиши